# Moru Wang

+86 17513365969 | wangmo@tcd.ie UI/UX designer

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a student recently graduated from Trinity College Dublin. I am passionate to be a UI/UX designer, I have a solid experience in full projects design and efficiently collaborate with other designers, developers and testers as a team. I equipped with a fast learning ability to quickly master new tools and tackle challenges with confidence.

#### **EDUCATION**

## North China University of Water Resources and Electric Power

Sep 2018 - Jul 2022

Electronic information engineering Bachelor

Zhengzhou

**Trinity College Dublin** 

Sep 2023 - Sep 2024

Interactive digital media Master

Dublin

## PROJECT EXPERIENCE

**NOMNOM** May 2024 - Aug 2024

Web designer and Visual designer

- The NOMNOM is a mobile app that recommends nearby restaurants based on cuisine type, ambiance and price, especially highlighting the top-rated cusine so that can save time for making choice and improve the posibility of good dining experience.
- Outline the questions with team and create a survey in Microsoft Forms to gather user requirements. Write the report after analyzing the survey result.
- Designed an interface in Figma including the design of buttons, icons, spacing, typography, color schemes and layout.
- Built the front end using React Native and Javascript, and collaborated with Node.js, Express, Axios, and MongoDB for back end functionality to bring a smooth and responsive interface

PLANDI Sep 2024 - Oct 2024

UI/UX designer and Web developer

- The PLANDI is a to-do app with social features which enables user to plan daily activities, book popular events, share photos and follow their friends.
- Conduct client meeting to gather information and draft reports to clarify user requirements.
- Create color scheme in Figma to enhance visual contrast across task categories, track statues and several responsive buttons.
- The core components including task, event, post and profile sections use React.js for front-end layout and Axios to interact with backend service.
- The MongoDB as the backend database received the request from frontend and manage user data to support real-time updates.

# **SKILLS & OTHERS**

- Design Skills: User research, Interaction design, Visual Design, Wireframing
- Technical Skills: HTML/CSS basics, Javascript, React.js, Data Analysis, Accessibility
- Design Tools: Figma, Adobe Ps, Adobe Ai

## **SCHOLARSHIPS**

- First-Class Academic Scholarship (Top 10%) North China University of Water Resources and Electric Power, 2021.
- Second-Class Student Scholarship (Top 15%) North China University of Water Resources and Electric Power, 2021.
- Third-Class Student Scholarship (Top 20%) North China University of Water Resources and Electric Power, 2020.
- Third-Class Academic Scholarship (Top 20%) North China University of Water Resources and Electric Power, 2020.